mmt.com.au 2019-03-12

# Privacy Policy - Multimedia Technology

This Privacy Policy applies to all personal information collected by Multimedia Technology Pty Ltd (Multimedia) directly or indirectly from you in the ordinary course of business.

## Protecting personal information

We at Multimedia are committed to protect personal privacy. Every individual has a right to control the collection & use of their personal information. Providing personal information is an act of trust. At Multimedia we consider this very seriously. Multimedia will use your personal information only for the purpose they were collected, unless consent is given otherwise.

## Collecting personal information

Multimedia will collect personal information when requested you to fill applications & forms, receive letters from you, over telephone queries, web queries & queries in person. We also collect information from credit reporting agencies, through trade references & third parties.

## Using personal information

Personal information may be used for following purposes:

  * To fulfil obligations under any sale or purchase contract or any other contract between the individual & Multimedia.
  * To assist in providing information about products, offers or any other special promotions.
  * To provide services offered by Multimedia.
  * To obtain opinions & comments about products or services.
  * To record as data for marketing analysis

## Using tracking technologies

Multimedia web site uses "cookies" to collect information related to access & browsing the web site, open or preview of pages. These devices help Multimedia to monitor and record the usage of different parts of the web site. Cookies do not identify users personally, although they identify the user's browser.

## Right to access, change & delete information

Individuals have the right to access and review their personal information available in the Multimedia database. This information may be amended by informing Multimedia in writing. Similarly a request could be made to delete such information. On receipt of request all reasonable steps will be taken to delete information unless it is not appropriate for legal reasons. Multimedia will unable to provide products and/or services to you on deletion of information.

## Disclosure of information

Personal information will be disclosed to other parties only after obtaining your consent. Your consent could be express or implied.

Multimedia may need to disclose your personal information to:

  * Your referee(s)
  * Credit reporting or debt collecting agencies
  * Our insurers
  * Your guarantors
  * Your authorised agent or your executor, administrator or legal representative.
  * Any other party who is authorised or required by law

## Contact by Multimedia

Multimedia may use your personal information to identify a product or service that may benefit you. Further Multimedia may contact you in time to time to inform you about new or existing products or services.

## Up to date & storage of information

Multimedia will take all necessary steps to ensure that your information we maintain are accurate and up- to- date. In the event you gain knowledge of inaccurate, incomplete or outdated information maintained by Multimedia, you should contact us immediately.

Multimedia will take reasonable step to keep all your personal information in a secure manner. All employees of Multimedia are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by the company.
